*************************** 1. row ***************************
                 id: 13284
            example: Nay, he could go farther than that, and venture to assert openly, over his own name, and leave on record for the benefit of posterity, _the assertion_ that this new method of inquiry _does apply_, directly and primarily, to those questions in which the human race are _primarily concerned_; that it strikes at once to the heart of those questions, and was invented to that end.
example_translation: 这是一个关于"首先主要地"的真实例句。
